<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<itemInfo>
	<itemKey>10222</itemKey>
	<itemName>Azwell Longbow of Temptation</itemName>
	<itemIcon>00010205.png</itemIcon>
	<itemDesc>The energy of Temptation is contained within this Azwell Longbow.\nIt can be developed by Refining a common Azwell Longbow.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Azwell Longbow of Temptation, Azwell Longbow</itemDesc>
	<house type="7">
		<item>
			<id>4601</id>
			<name>Ash Timber</name>
			<icon>00004601.png</icon>
			<desc>A Processed natural resource obtained through Gathering and used as a material for Crafting. It can be modified using Alchemy or further Processing.\n- How to Obtain: It can be Produced at Goblin Cave, Ehwaz Hill, Balenos Forest, and Wolf Hills. It can be also be obtained by Lumbering Ash Trees.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>4059</id>
			<name>Pure Copper Crystal</name>
			<icon>00004059.png</icon>
			<desc>A Processed natural resource obtained through Gathering and used as a material for Crafting. It can be modified using Alchemy or further Processing.\n\n- How to Obtain: It can be obtained by Heating Metal Solvent acquired by Alchemy and Copper Ingots. It requires the knowledge of Heating: Skilled.\n\n※ Find Vatudun in Keplan and complete the Materials for Skills Quest to obtain related knowledge.\n\n※ In order to perform the related Quest, achieve Gathering Professional Level 10 and Processing Professional Level 5. Refer to the Black Spirit Guide (/key) for detailed information.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>6160</id>
			<name>Fine Tough Hide</name>
			<icon>00006160.png</icon>
			<desc>A Processed natural resource obtained through Gathering and used as a material for Crafting. It can be modified using Alchemy or further Processing.\n\n- How to Obtain: It can be obtained by Drying rhino, pig, or cow hide. It requires the knowledge of Drying: Beginner.\n\n※ Find Techthon in Heidel and complete the Need for Soft Hide! Quest to obtain related knowledge.\n\n※ In order to perform the related Quest, achieve Gathering Level 14 or higher. Refer to the Black Spirit Guide (/key) for detailed information.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>4901</id>
			<name>Black Stone Powder</name>
			<icon>00004901.png</icon>
			<desc>A basic ingredient used in Crafting.\n- How to Obtain: It can be obtained at a Refinery through Crafting.</desc>
		</item>
	</house>
	<house type="11">
		<item>
			<id>10205</id>
			<name>Azwell Longbow</name>
			<icon>00010205.png</icon>
			<desc>A longbow custom-made for the commander of the Militia.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>4906</id>
			<name>Grade 1 Weapon Reform Stone</name>
			<icon>00004906.png</icon>
			<desc>A material used in 1st-grade weapon upgrade.\n-Obtainable from: Refinery, through crafting.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>4901</id>
			<name>Black Stone Powder</name>
			<icon>00004901.png</icon>
			<desc>A basic ingredient used in Crafting.\n- How to Obtain: It can be obtained at a Refinery through Crafting.</desc>
		</item>
	</house>
	<makelist>
		<item>
			<id>10205</id>
			<name>Azwell Longbow</name>
			<icon>00010205.png</icon>
			<desc>A longbow custom-made for the commander of the Militia.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10222</id>
			<name>Azwell Longbow of Temptation</name>
			<icon>00010205.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Temptation is contained within this Azwell Longbow.\nIt can be developed by Refining a common Azwell Longbow.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Azwell Longbow of Temptation, Azwell Longbow</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10221</id>
			<name>Azwell Longbow of Destruction</name>
			<icon>00010205.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Destruction is contained within this Azwell Longbow.\nIt can be developed by Refining a common Azwell Longbow.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Azwell Longbow of Destruction, Azwell Longbow</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10220</id>
			<name>Azwell Longbow of Crimson Flame</name>
			<icon>00010205.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Crimson Flame is contained within this Azwell Longbow.\nIt can be developed by Refining a common Azwell Longbow.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Azwell Longbow of Crimson Flame, Azwell Longbow</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10223</id>
			<name>Ultimate Azwell Longbow</name>
			<icon>00010205.png</icon>
			<desc>An Azwell Longbow developed to its maximum potential.\nThere is a small chance this will be developed when Refining a common Azwell Longbow.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Azwell Longbow of Crimson Flame, Azwell Longbow of Destruction, Azwell Longbow of Temptation, Azwell Longbow</desc>
		</item>
	</makelist>
</itemInfo>

