<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<itemInfo>
	<itemKey>10231</itemKey>
	<itemName>Ultimate Seleth Longbow</itemName>
	<itemIcon>00010207.png</itemIcon>
	<itemDesc>A Seleth Longbow developed to its maximum potential.\nThere is a small chance this will be developed when Refining a common Seleth Longbow.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Seleth Longbow of Crimson Flame, Seleth Longbow of Destruction, Seleth Longbow of Temptation, Seleth Longbow</itemDesc>
	<house type="7">
		<item>
			<id>4603</id>
			<name>Pine Timber</name>
			<icon>00004603.png</icon>
			<desc>A Processed natural resource obtained through Gathering and used as a material for Crafting. It can be modified using Alchemy or further Processing.\n- How to Obtain: It can be Produced at Serendia Shrine and Marie Cave. It can be also be obtained by Lumbering Pine Trees.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>4056</id>
			<name>Pure Lead Crystal</name>
			<icon>00004056.png</icon>
			<desc>A Processed natural resource obtained through Gathering and used as a material for Crafting. It can be modified using Alchemy or further Processing.\n\n- How to Obtain: It can be obtained by Heating Metal Solvent acquired by Alchemy and Lead Ingots. It requires the knowledge of Heating: Skilled.\n\n※ Find Vatudun in Keplan and complete the Materials for Skills Quest to obtain related knowledge.\n\n※ In order to perform the related Quest, achieve Gathering Professional Level 10 and Processing Professional Level 5. Refer to the Black Spirit Guide (/key) for detailed information.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>6160</id>
			<name>Fine Tough Hide</name>
			<icon>00006160.png</icon>
			<desc>A Processed natural resource obtained through Gathering and used as a material for Crafting. It can be modified using Alchemy or further Processing.\n\n- How to Obtain: It can be obtained by Drying rhino, pig, or cow hide. It requires the knowledge of Drying: Beginner.\n\n※ Find Techthon in Heidel and complete the Need for Soft Hide! Quest to obtain related knowledge.\n\n※ In order to perform the related Quest, achieve Gathering Level 14 or higher. Refer to the Black Spirit Guide (/key) for detailed information.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>5962</id>
			<name>Trace of Death</name>
			<icon>00005962.png</icon>
			<desc>A material used for Crafting equipment. It can be obtained through Excavation.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>4901</id>
			<name>Black Stone Powder</name>
			<icon>00004901.png</icon>
			<desc>A basic ingredient used in Crafting.\n- How to Obtain: It can be obtained at a Refinery through Crafting.</desc>
		</item>
	</house>
	<house type="11">
		<item>
			<id>10228</id>
			<name>Seleth Longbow of Crimson Flame</name>
			<icon>00010207.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Crimson Flame is contained within this Seleth Longbow.\nIt can be developed by Refining a common Seleth Longbow.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Seleth Longbow of Crimson Flame, Seleth Longbow</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>4910</id>
			<name>Grade 3 Weapon Reform Stone</name>
			<icon>00004910.png</icon>
			<desc>A material used in 3rd-grade weapon upgrade.\n-Obtainable from: Refinery, through crafting.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>4901</id>
			<name>Black Stone Powder</name>
			<icon>00004901.png</icon>
			<desc>A basic ingredient used in Crafting.\n- How to Obtain: It can be obtained at a Refinery through Crafting.</desc>
		</item>
	</house>
	<makelist>
		<item>
			<id>10207</id>
			<name>Seleth Longbow</name>
			<icon>00010207.png</icon>
			<desc>A longbow possessed with a strong hatred for Humankind.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10229</id>
			<name>Seleth Longbow of Destruction</name>
			<icon>00010207.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Destruction is contained within this Seleth Longbow.\nIt can be developed by Refining a common Seleth Longbow.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Seleth Longbow of Destruction, Seleth Longbow</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10228</id>
			<name>Seleth Longbow of Crimson Flame</name>
			<icon>00010207.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Crimson Flame is contained within this Seleth Longbow.\nIt can be developed by Refining a common Seleth Longbow.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Seleth Longbow of Crimson Flame, Seleth Longbow</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10230</id>
			<name>Seleth Longbow of Temptation</name>
			<icon>00010207.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Temptation is contained within this Seleth Longbow.\nIt can be developed by Refining a common Seleth Longbow.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Seleth Longbow of Temptation, Seleth Longbow</desc>
		</item>
	</makelist>
</itemInfo>

