<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<itemInfo>
	<itemKey>14122</itemKey>
	<itemName>Ultimate Steel Taritas Armor</itemName>
	<itemIcon>00010814.png</itemIcon>
	<itemDesc>Steel Taritas Armor with maximum potential.\nLighter than ordinary Ultimate Taritas armor, and more durable.\n- Equipping 2 or more parts will trigger the set effect\n- Restore Max Durability : All Taritas and Steel Taritas Armor</itemDesc>
	<house type="5">
		<item>
			<id>4077</id>
			<name>Steel</name>
			<icon>00004077.png</icon>
			<desc>A Processed natural resource obtained through Gathering and used as a material for Crafting. It can be modified using Alchemy or further Processing.\n\n- How to Obtain: It can be obtained by Heating Melted Iron Shards and Coal together. It requires the knowledge of Heating: Beginner.\n\n※ Find Flaviano in Heidel and complete the Pure Water for an Experiment Quest to obtain related knowledge.\n\n※ In order to perform the Quest for Beginner Processing knowledge, achieve Gathering Apprentice Level 4 or higher and visit Ficy in Heidel to complete the corresponding Quest. Refer to the Black Spirit Guide (/key) for detailed information.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>6161</id>
			<name>Fine Hard Hide</name>
			<icon>00006161.png</icon>
			<desc>A Processed natural resource obtained through Gathering and used as a material for Crafting. It can be modified using Alchemy or further Processing.\n\n- How to Obtain: It can be obtained by Drying dinosaur, lizard, or worm hide. It requires the knowledge of Drying: Beginner.\n\n※ Find Techthon in Heidel and complete the Need for Soft Hide! Quest to obtain related knowledge.\n\n※ In order to perform the related Quest, achieve Gathering Level 14 or higher. Refer to the Black Spirit Guide (/key) for detailed information.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>4901</id>
			<name>Black Stone Powder</name>
			<icon>00004901.png</icon>
			<desc>A basic ingredient used in Crafting.\n- How to Obtain: It can be obtained at a Refinery through Crafting.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>4467</id>
			<name>Mud Crystal</name>
			<icon>00004467.png</icon>
			<desc>A Processed natural resource obtained through Gathering and used as a material for Crafting. It can be modified using Alchemy or further Processing.\n- How to Obtain: It can be obtained by Heating Rough Mud Crystals found near Glish Ruins.</desc>
		</item>
	</house>
	<house type="11">
		<item>
			<id>14106</id>
			<name>Steel Taritas Armor of Iron Wall</name>
			<icon>00010814.png</icon>
			<desc>Energy of iron wall is contained within this Steel Taritas Armor\nLighter than ordinary Taritas Armor of Iron Wall, and more durable.\n- Equipping 2 or more parts will trigger the set effect\n- Restore Max Durability : Steel Taritas Armor of Iron wall, Steel Taritas Armor, Taritas Armor</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>4911</id>
			<name>Grade 3 Armor Reform Stone</name>
			<icon>00004911.png</icon>
			<desc>A material used in 3rd-grade armor upgrade.\n-Obtainable from: Refinery, through crafting.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>4901</id>
			<name>Black Stone Powder</name>
			<icon>00004901.png</icon>
			<desc>A basic ingredient used in Crafting.\n- How to Obtain: It can be obtained at a Refinery through Crafting.</desc>
		</item>
	</house>
	<makelist>
		<item>
			<id>14102</id>
			<name>Steel Taritas Armor</name>
			<icon>00010814.png</icon>
			<desc>Steel Taritas Armor made by master blacksmith\nIt is lighter and more durable than normal one. It can also be used for durability restoration of normal Taritas Armor.\n- Equipping 2 or more parts will trigger the set effect</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>14110</id>
			<name>Steel Taritas Armor of Agility</name>
			<icon>00010814.png</icon>
			<desc>Energy of agility is contained within this Steel Taritas Armor\nLighter than ordinary Taritas Armor of Agility, and more durable.\n- Equipping 2 or more parts will trigger the set effect\n- Restore Max Durability : Steel Taritas Armor of Agility, Steel Taritas Armor, Taritas Armor</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>14106</id>
			<name>Steel Taritas Armor of Iron Wall</name>
			<icon>00010814.png</icon>
			<desc>Energy of iron wall is contained within this Steel Taritas Armor\nLighter than ordinary Taritas Armor of Iron Wall, and more durable.\n- Equipping 2 or more parts will trigger the set effect\n- Restore Max Durability : Steel Taritas Armor of Iron wall, Steel Taritas Armor, Taritas Armor</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>14114</id>
			<name>Steel Taritas Armor of Intimidation</name>
			<icon>00010814.png</icon>
			<desc>Energy of intimidation is contained within this Steel Taritas Armor\nLighter than ordinary Taritas Armor of Duress, and more durable.\n- Equipping 2 or more parts will trigger the set effect\n- Restore Max Durability : Steel Taritas Armor of Duress, Steel Taritas Armor, Taritas Armor</desc>
		</item>
	</makelist>
</itemInfo>

