<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<itemInfo>
	<itemKey>14424</itemKey>
	<itemName>Demihuman Staff of Crimson Flame</itemName>
	<itemIcon>00014406.png</itemIcon>
	<itemDesc>The energy of Crimson Flame is contained within this Demihuman Staff.\nIt can be developed by Refining a common Demihuman Staff.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Demihuman Staff of Crimson Flame, Demihuman Staff</itemDesc>
	<house type="6">
		<item>
			<id>4062</id>
			<name>Pure Tin Crystal</name>
			<icon>00004062.png</icon>
			<desc>A Processed natural resource obtained through Gathering and used as a material for Crafting. It can be modified using Alchemy or further Processing.\n\n- How to Obtain: It can be obtained by Heating Metal Solvent acquired by Alchemy and Tin Ingots. It requires the knowledge of Heating: Skilled.\n\n※ Find Vatudun in Keplan and complete the Materials for Skills Quest to obtain related knowledge.\n\n※ In order to perform the related Quest, achieve Gathering Professional Level 10 and Processing Professional Level 5. Refer to the Black Spirit Guide (/key) for detailed information.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>5001</id>
			<name>Ash Sap</name>
			<icon>00005001.png</icon>
			<desc>A natural resource obtained through Gathering that can be employed to modify other materials using Alchemy.\n- How to Obtain: It can be obtained from an Ash Tree using a Fluid Collector.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>4601</id>
			<name>Ash Timber</name>
			<icon>00004601.png</icon>
			<desc>A Processed natural resource obtained through Gathering and used as a material for Crafting. It can be modified using Alchemy or further Processing.\n- How to Obtain: It can be Produced at Goblin Cave, Ehwaz Hill, Balenos Forest, and Wolf Hills. It can be also be obtained by Lumbering Ash Trees.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>5007</id>
			<name>Monk&apos;s Branch</name>
			<icon>00005007.png</icon>
			<desc>A natural resource obtained through Gathering that can be employed to modify other materials using Alchemy. Monk&apos;s Branch requires a certain level of skill to collect.\n- How to Obtain: This alchemical ingredient can be obtained by Lumbering trees, but only rarely.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>5956</id>
			<name>Trace of Savagery</name>
			<icon>00005956.png</icon>
			<desc>A material used for Crafting equipment.\nIt can be Excavated at Lynch Farm Ruins.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>4901</id>
			<name>Black Stone Powder</name>
			<icon>00004901.png</icon>
			<desc>A basic ingredient used in Crafting.\n- How to Obtain: It can be obtained at a Refinery through Crafting.</desc>
		</item>
	</house>
	<house type="11">
		<item>
			<id>14406</id>
			<name>Demihuman Staff</name>
			<icon>00014406.png</icon>
			<desc>A staff made for fighting threats to Humankind.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>4906</id>
			<name>Grade 1 Weapon Reform Stone</name>
			<icon>00004906.png</icon>
			<desc>A material used in 1st-grade weapon upgrade.\n-Obtainable from: Refinery, through crafting.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>4901</id>
			<name>Black Stone Powder</name>
			<icon>00004901.png</icon>
			<desc>A basic ingredient used in Crafting.\n- How to Obtain: It can be obtained at a Refinery through Crafting.</desc>
		</item>
	</house>
	<makelist>
		<item>
			<id>14427</id>
			<name>Ultimate Demihuman Staff</name>
			<icon>00014406.png</icon>
			<desc>A Demihuman staff at its maximum potential.\nIt has a low chance of being crafted when upgrading a Demihuman staff.\n\n- Restore Max Durability: Demihuman Staff of Crimson Flame, Demihuman Staff of Destruction, Demihuman Staff of Temptation, Demihuman Staff</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>14426</id>
			<name>Demihuman Staff of Temptation</name>
			<icon>00014406.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Temptation is contained within this Demihuman Staff.\nIt can be developed by Refining a common Demihuman Staff.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Demihuman Staff of Temptation, Demihuman Staff</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>14425</id>
			<name>Demihuman Staff of Destruction</name>
			<icon>00014406.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Destruction is contained within this Demihuman Staff.\nIt can be developed by Refining a common Demihuman Staff.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Demihuman Staff of Destruction, Demihuman Staff</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>14424</id>
			<name>Demihuman Staff of Crimson Flame</name>
			<icon>00014406.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Crimson Flame is contained within this Demihuman Staff.\nIt can be developed by Refining a common Demihuman Staff.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Demihuman Staff of Crimson Flame, Demihuman Staff</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>14406</id>
			<name>Demihuman Staff</name>
			<icon>00014406.png</icon>
			<desc>A staff made for fighting threats to Humankind.</desc>
		</item>
	</makelist>
</itemInfo>

