<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<itemInfo>
	<itemKey>14428</itemKey>
	<itemName>Seleth Staff of Crimson Flame</itemName>
	<itemIcon>00014407.png</itemIcon>
	<itemDesc>The energy of Crimson Flame is contained within this Seleth Staff.\nIt can be developed by Refining a common Seleth Staff.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Seleth Staff of Crimson Flame, Seleth Staff</itemDesc>
	<house type="6">
		<item>
			<id>4077</id>
			<name>Steel</name>
			<icon>00004077.png</icon>
			<desc>A Processed natural resource obtained through Gathering and used as a material for Crafting. It can be modified using Alchemy or further Processing.\n\n- How to Obtain: It can be obtained by Heating Melted Iron Shards and Coal together. It requires the knowledge of Heating: Beginner.\n\n※ Find Flaviano in Heidel and complete the Pure Water for an Experiment Quest to obtain related knowledge.\n\n※ In order to perform the Quest for Beginner Processing knowledge, achieve Gathering Apprentice Level 4 or higher and visit Ficy in Heidel to complete the corresponding Quest. Refer to the Black Spirit Guide (/key) for detailed information.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>5001</id>
			<name>Ash Sap</name>
			<icon>00005001.png</icon>
			<desc>A natural resource obtained through Gathering that can be employed to modify other materials using Alchemy.\n- How to Obtain: It can be obtained from an Ash Tree using a Fluid Collector.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>4601</id>
			<name>Ash Timber</name>
			<icon>00004601.png</icon>
			<desc>A Processed natural resource obtained through Gathering and used as a material for Crafting. It can be modified using Alchemy or further Processing.\n- How to Obtain: It can be Produced at Goblin Cave, Ehwaz Hill, Balenos Forest, and Wolf Hills. It can be also be obtained by Lumbering Ash Trees.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>5007</id>
			<name>Monk&apos;s Branch</name>
			<icon>00005007.png</icon>
			<desc>A natural resource obtained through Gathering that can be employed to modify other materials using Alchemy. Monk&apos;s Branch requires a certain level of skill to collect.\n- How to Obtain: This alchemical ingredient can be obtained by Lumbering trees, but only rarely.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>5962</id>
			<name>Trace of Death</name>
			<icon>00005962.png</icon>
			<desc>A material used for Crafting equipment. It can be obtained through Excavation.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>4901</id>
			<name>Black Stone Powder</name>
			<icon>00004901.png</icon>
			<desc>A basic ingredient used in Crafting.\n- How to Obtain: It can be obtained at a Refinery through Crafting.</desc>
		</item>
	</house>
	<house type="11">
		<item>
			<id>14407</id>
			<name>Seleth Staff</name>
			<icon>00014407.png</icon>
			<desc>A staff possessed with a strong hatred for Humankind.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>4906</id>
			<name>Grade 1 Weapon Reform Stone</name>
			<icon>00004906.png</icon>
			<desc>A material used in 1st-grade weapon upgrade.\n-Obtainable from: Refinery, through crafting.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>4901</id>
			<name>Black Stone Powder</name>
			<icon>00004901.png</icon>
			<desc>A basic ingredient used in Crafting.\n- How to Obtain: It can be obtained at a Refinery through Crafting.</desc>
		</item>
	</house>
	<makelist>
		<item>
			<id>14431</id>
			<name>Ultimate Seleth Staff</name>
			<icon>00014407.png</icon>
			<desc>A Seleth staff at its maximum potential.\nIt has a low chance of being crafted when upgrading a Seleth staff.\n\n- Restore Max Durability: Seleth Staff of Crimson Flame, Seleth Staff of Destruction, Seleth Staff of Temptation, Seleth Staff</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>14430</id>
			<name>Seleth Staff of Temptation</name>
			<icon>00014407.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Temptation is contained within this Seleth Staff.\nIt can be developed by Refining a common Seleth Staff.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Seleth Staff of Temptation, Seleth Staff</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>14429</id>
			<name>Seleth Staff of Destruction</name>
			<icon>00014407.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Destruction is contained within this Seleth Staff.\nIt can be developed by Refining a common Seleth Staff.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Seleth Staff of Destruction, Seleth Staff</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>14428</id>
			<name>Seleth Staff of Crimson Flame</name>
			<icon>00014407.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Crimson Flame is contained within this Seleth Staff.\nIt can be developed by Refining a common Seleth Staff.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Seleth Staff of Crimson Flame, Seleth Staff</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>14407</id>
			<name>Seleth Staff</name>
			<icon>00014407.png</icon>
			<desc>A staff possessed with a strong hatred for Humankind.</desc>
		</item>
	</makelist>
</itemInfo>

