<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<itemInfo>
	<itemKey>14459</itemKey>
	<itemName>Krea Staff of Destruction</itemName>
	<itemIcon>00014456.png</itemIcon>
	<itemDesc>The energy of Destruction is contained within this Krea Staff.\nIt can be developed by Refining a common Krea Staff.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Krea Staff of Destruction, Krea Staff</itemDesc>
	<house type="6">
		<item>
			<id>4253</id>
			<name>Pure Silver Crystal</name>
			<icon>00004253.png</icon>
			<desc>A Processed natural resource obtained through Gathering and used as a material for Crafting. It can be modified using Alchemy or further Processing.\n\n- How to Obtain: It can be obtained by Heating Metal Solvent acquired by Alchemy and Silver Ingots. It requires the knowledge of Heating: Skilled.\n\n※ Find Vatudun in Keplan and complete the Materials for Skills Quest to obtain related knowledge.\n\n※ In order to perform the related Quest, achieve Gathering Professional Level 10 and Processing Professional Level 5. Refer to the Black Spirit Guide (/key) for detailed information.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>5004</id>
			<name>Birch Sap</name>
			<icon>00005004.png</icon>
			<desc>A natural resource obtained through Gathering that can be employed to modify other materials using Alchemy.\n- How to Obtain: It can be obtained from Birch Trees with a Fluid Collector.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>4604</id>
			<name>Birch Timber</name>
			<icon>00004604.png</icon>
			<desc>A Processed natural resource obtained through Gathering and used as a material for Crafting. It can be modified using Alchemy or further Processing.\n- How to Obtain: It can be Produced at Quint Hill, Bree Tree Ruins, and Old Dandelion. It can be also be obtained by Lumbering Birch Trees.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>5007</id>
			<name>Monk&apos;s Branch</name>
			<icon>00005007.png</icon>
			<desc>A natural resource obtained through Gathering that can be employed to modify other materials using Alchemy. Monk&apos;s Branch requires a certain level of skill to collect.\n- How to Obtain: This alchemical ingredient can be obtained by Lumbering trees, but only rarely.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>5952</id>
			<name>Trace of Despair</name>
			<icon>00005952.png</icon>
			<desc>A material used for Crafting equipment.\nIt can be Excavated at Rhua Tree Stub and Mansha Forest.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>4901</id>
			<name>Black Stone Powder</name>
			<icon>00004901.png</icon>
			<desc>A basic ingredient used in Crafting.\n- How to Obtain: It can be obtained at a Refinery through Crafting.</desc>
		</item>
	</house>
	<house type="11">
		<item>
			<id>14456</id>
			<name>Krea Staff</name>
			<icon>00014456.png</icon>
			<desc>A staff crafted to meet the strict requirements of adventurers.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>4906</id>
			<name>Grade 1 Weapon Reform Stone</name>
			<icon>00004906.png</icon>
			<desc>A material used in 1st-grade weapon upgrade.\n-Obtainable from: Refinery, through crafting.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>4901</id>
			<name>Black Stone Powder</name>
			<icon>00004901.png</icon>
			<desc>A basic ingredient used in Crafting.\n- How to Obtain: It can be obtained at a Refinery through Crafting.</desc>
		</item>
	</house>
	<makelist>
		<item>
			<id>14456</id>
			<name>Krea Staff</name>
			<icon>00014456.png</icon>
			<desc>A staff crafted to meet the strict requirements of adventurers.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>14463</id>
			<name>Ultimate Krea Staff</name>
			<icon>00014456.png</icon>
			<desc>A Krea staff at its maximum potential.\nIt has a low chance of being crafted when upgrading a Krea staff.\n\n- Restore Max Durability: Krea Staff of Crimson Flame, Krea Staff of Destruction, Krea Staff of Temptation, Krea Staff</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>14460</id>
			<name>Krea Staff of Temptation</name>
			<icon>00014456.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Temptation is contained within this Krea Staff.\nIt can be developed by Refining a common Krea Staff.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Krea Staff of Temptation, Krea Staff</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>14459</id>
			<name>Krea Staff of Destruction</name>
			<icon>00014456.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Destruction is contained within this Krea Staff.\nIt can be developed by Refining a common Krea Staff.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Krea Staff of Destruction, Krea Staff</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>14458</id>
			<name>Krea Staff of Crimson Flame</name>
			<icon>00014456.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Crimson Flame is contained within this Krea Staff.\nIt can be developed by Refining a common Krea Staff.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Krea Staff of Crimson Flame, Krea Staff</desc>
		</item>
	</makelist>
</itemInfo>

