<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<itemInfo>
	<itemKey>2204</itemKey>
	<itemName>Velian Handcrafted Dining Table</itemName>
	<itemIcon>InHouse_D_DFF_Table_01.png</itemIcon>
	<itemDesc>A handcrafted dining table from Velia.\n- 4 Set Effect: Interior Points +200</itemDesc>
	<house type="16">
		<item>
			<id>4652</id>
			<name>Ash Plywood</name>
			<icon>00004652.png</icon>
			<desc>A Processed natural resource obtained through Gathering and used as a material for Crafting. It can be modified using Alchemy or further Processing.\n\n- How to Obtain: It can be also be obtained by Chopping Ash Timber. It requires Chopping: Beginner knowledge.\n\n※ Find Lebyos in Heidel and complete the Working the Ash Tree Quest to obtain related knowledge.\n\n※ In order to perform the Quest for Beginner Processing knowledge, achieve Gathering Level 14 or higher and visit Ficy in Heidel to complete the corresponding Quest. Refer to the Black Spirit Guide (/key) for detailed information.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>4605</id>
			<name>Log</name>
			<icon>00004605.png</icon>
			<desc>A Processed natural resource obtained through Gathering and used as a material for Crafting. It can be modified using Alchemy or further Processing.\n- How to Obtain: It can be obtained by Lumbering trees grown in every region.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>4067</id>
			<name>Bronze Ingot</name>
			<icon>00004067.png</icon>
			<desc>A Processed natural resource obtained through Gathering and used as a material for Crafting. It can be modified using Alchemy or further Processing.\n\n- How to Obtain: It can be obtained by Heating Copper and Tin together. It requires the knowledge of Heating: Beginner.\n\n※ Find Flaviano in Heidel and complete the Pure Water for an Experiment Quest to obtain related knowledge.\n\n※ In order to perform the Quest for Beginner Processing knowledge, achieve Gathering Apprentice Level 4 or higher and visit Ficy in Heidel to complete the corresponding Quest. Refer to the Black Spirit Guide (/key) for detailed information.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>4901</id>
			<name>Black Stone Powder</name>
			<icon>00004901.png</icon>
			<desc>A basic ingredient used in Crafting.\n- How to Obtain: It can be obtained at a Refinery through Crafting.</desc>
		</item>
	</house>
</itemInfo>

