<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<itemInfo>
	<itemKey>2702</itemKey>
	<itemName>Heidel Handcrafted Bed</itemName>
	<itemIcon>InHouse_B_DFF_Bed_01.png</itemIcon>
	<itemDesc>A handcrafted bed from Heidel.\n- 4 Set Effect: Interior Points +200</itemDesc>
	<house type="16">
		<item>
			<id>4656</id>
			<name>Sturdy Maple Plywood</name>
			<icon>00004656.png</icon>
			<desc>A processed natural resource obtained through Gathering and used as a material for Crafting. It can be modified using Alchemy or further Processing.\n- How to Obtain: It can be obtained by Heating Plywood Hardener and Maple Plywood. It requires the knowledge of Heating: Skilled.\n※ Find Vatudun in Keplan and complete the Materials for Skills Quest to obtain related knowledge.\n※ In order to perform the related Quest, achieve Gathering Professional Level 10 and Processing Professional Level 5. Refer to the Black Spirit Guide (/key) for detailed information.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>4669</id>
			<name>Usable Scantling</name>
			<icon>00004669.png</icon>
			<desc>Timber required for Construction.\n\n- How to Obtain: It can be also be obtained by Chopping Logs received from trees Lumbered in any region.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>4067</id>
			<name>Bronze Ingot</name>
			<icon>00004067.png</icon>
			<desc>A Processed natural resource obtained through Gathering and used as a material for Crafting. It can be modified using Alchemy or further Processing.\n\n- How to Obtain: It can be obtained by Heating Copper and Tin together. It requires the knowledge of Heating: Beginner.\n\n※ Find Flaviano in Heidel and complete the Pure Water for an Experiment Quest to obtain related knowledge.\n\n※ In order to perform the Quest for Beginner Processing knowledge, achieve Gathering Apprentice Level 4 or higher and visit Ficy in Heidel to complete the corresponding Quest. Refer to the Black Spirit Guide (/key) for detailed information.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>4901</id>
			<name>Black Stone Powder</name>
			<icon>00004901.png</icon>
			<desc>A basic ingredient used in Crafting.\n- How to Obtain: It can be obtained at a Refinery through Crafting.</desc>
		</item>
	</house>
</itemInfo>

