<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<itemInfo>
	<itemKey>4259</itemKey>
	<itemName>Pure Platinum Crystal</itemName>
	<itemIcon>00004259.png</itemIcon>
	<itemDesc>A Processed natural resource obtained through Gathering and used as a material for Crafting. It can be modified using Alchemy or further Processing.\n\n- How to Obtain: It can be obtained by Heating Metal Solvent acquired by Alchemy and Platinum Ingots. It requires the knowledge of Heating: Skilled.\n\n※ Find Vatudun in Keplan and complete the Materials for Skills Quest to obtain related knowledge.\n\n※ In order to perform the related Quest, achieve Gathering Professional Level 10 and Processing Professional Level 5. Refer to the Black Spirit Guide (/key) for detailed information.</itemDesc>
	<manufacture action="MANUFACTURE_HEAT">
		<item>
			<id>4076</id>
			<name>Metal Solvent</name>
			<icon>00004076.png</icon>
			<desc>A material used to change metals into a pure crystal form through Processing.\n\n- How to Obtain: It can be obtained through Alchemy.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>4258</id>
			<name>Platinum Ingot</name>
			<icon>00004258.png</icon>
			<desc>A Processed natural resource obtained through Gathering and used as a material for Crafting. It can be modified using Alchemy or further Processing.\n\n- How to Obtain: It can be obtained by Heating Platinum Ore. It requires the knowledge of Heating: Beginner.\n\n※ Find Flaviano in Heidel and complete the Pure Water for an Experiment Quest to obtain related knowledge.\n\n※ In order to perform the Quest for Beginner Processing knowledge, achieve Gathering Level 14 or higher and visit Ficy in Heidel to complete the corresponding Quest. Refer to the Black Spirit Guide (/key) for detailed information.</desc>
		</item>
	</manufacture>
	<manufacture action="MANUFACTURE_HEAT">
		<item>
			<id>10013</id>
			<name>Bares Longsword</name>
			<icon>00010013.png</icon>
			<desc>A longsword possessed with a hatred for all living things.</desc>
		</item>
	</manufacture>
	<manufacture action="MANUFACTURE_HEAT">
		<item>
			<id>10213</id>
			<name>Bares Longbow</name>
			<icon>00010213.png</icon>
			<desc>A longbow possessed with a hatred for all living things.</desc>
		</item>
	</manufacture>
	<manufacture action="MANUFACTURE_HEAT">
		<item>
			<id>10413</id>
			<name>Bares Amulet</name>
			<icon>00010413.png</icon>
			<desc>An amulet possessed with a hatred for all living things.</desc>
		</item>
	</manufacture>
	<manufacture action="MANUFACTURE_HEAT">
		<item>
			<id>10613</id>
			<name>Bares Axe</name>
			<icon>00010613.png</icon>
			<desc>An axe possessed with a hatred for all living things.</desc>
		</item>
	</manufacture>
	<manufacture action="MANUFACTURE_HEAT">
		<item>
			<id>13213</id>
			<name>Bares Shortsword</name>
			<icon>00013207.png</icon>
			<desc>A Shortsword possessed with a hatred for all living things.</desc>
		</item>
	</manufacture>
	<manufacture action="MANUFACTURE_HEAT">
		<item>
			<id>14413</id>
			<name>Bares Staff</name>
			<icon>00014413.png</icon>
			<desc>A staff possessed with a hatred for all living things.</desc>
		</item>
	</manufacture>
	<makelist>
		<item>
			<id>14413</id>
			<name>Bares Staff</name>
			<icon>00014413.png</icon>
			<desc>A staff possessed with a hatred for all living things.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>14437</id>
			<name>Bares Staff of Destruction</name>
			<icon>00014413.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Destruction is contained within this Bares Staff.\nIt can be developed by Refining a common Bares Staff.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Bares Staff of Destruction, Bares Staff</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>14436</id>
			<name>Bares Staff of Crimson Flame</name>
			<icon>00014413.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Crimson Flame is contained within this Bares Staff.\nIt can be developed by Refining a common Bares Staff.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Bares Staff of Crimson Flame, Bares Staff</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>11715</id>
			<name>Topaz Necklace of Regeneration</name>
			<icon>00011715.png</icon>
			<desc>A necklace decorated with a Topaz of Regeneration.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>12105</id>
			<name>Corrupt Ruby Ring</name>
			<icon>00012105.png</icon>
			<desc>A ring decorated with a Corrupt Ruby.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>11915</id>
			<name>Topaz Earrings of Regeneration</name>
			<icon>00011915.png</icon>
			<desc>An earring decorated with a Topaz of Regeneration.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>13213</id>
			<name>Bares Shortsword</name>
			<icon>00013207.png</icon>
			<desc>A Shortsword possessed with a hatred for all living things.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>13237</id>
			<name>Bares Shortsword of Destruction</name>
			<icon>00013207.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Destruction is contained within this Bares Shortsword.\nIt can be developed by Refining a common Bares Shortsword.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Bares Shortsword of Destruction, Bares Shortsword</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>13236</id>
			<name>Bares Shortsword of Crimson Flame</name>
			<icon>00013207.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Crimson Flame is contained within this Bares Shortsword.\nIt can be developed by Refining a common Bares Shortsword.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Bares Shortsword of Crimson Flame, Bares Shortsword</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>13239</id>
			<name>Ultimate Bares Shortsword</name>
			<icon>00013207.png</icon>
			<desc>A Bares Shortsword developed to its maximum potential.\nThere is a small chance this will be developed when Refining a common Bares Shortsword.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Bares Shortsword of Crimson Flame, Bares Shortsword of Destruction, Bares Shortsword of Temptation, Bares Shortsword</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>13238</id>
			<name>Bares Shortsword of Temptation</name>
			<icon>00013207.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Temptation is contained within this Bares Shortsword.\nIt can be developed by Refining a common Bares Shortsword.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Bares Shortsword of Temptation, Bares Shortsword</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10413</id>
			<name>Bares Amulet</name>
			<icon>00010413.png</icon>
			<desc>An amulet possessed with a hatred for all living things.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10439</id>
			<name>Ultimate Bares Amulet</name>
			<icon>00010413.png</icon>
			<desc>A Bares Amulet developed to its maximum potential.\nThere is a small chance this will be developed when Refining a common Bares Amulet.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Bares Amulet of Crimson Flame, Bares Amulet of Destruction, Bares Amulet of Temptation, Bares Amulet</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10438</id>
			<name>Bares Amulet of Temptation</name>
			<icon>00010413.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Temptation is contained within this Bares Amulet.\nIt can be developed by Refining a common Bares Amulet.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Bares Amulet of Temptation, Bares Amulet</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10437</id>
			<name>Bares Amulet of Destruction</name>
			<icon>00010413.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Destruction is contained within this Bares Amulet.\nIt can be developed by Refining a common Bares Amulet.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Bares Amulet of Destruction, Bares Amulet</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10436</id>
			<name>Bares Amulet of Crimson Flame</name>
			<icon>00010413.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Crimson Flame is contained within this Bares Amulet.\nIt can be developed by Refining a common Bares Amulet.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Bares Amulet of Crimson Flame, Bares Amulet</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>14439</id>
			<name>Ultimate Bares Staff</name>
			<icon>00014413.png</icon>
			<desc>A Bares staff at its maximum potential.\nIt has a low chance of being crafted when upgrading a Bares staff.\n\n- Restore Max Durability: Bares Staff of Crimson Flame, Bares Staff of Destruction, Bares Staff of Temptation, Bares Staff</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>14438</id>
			<name>Bares Staff of Temptation</name>
			<icon>00014413.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Temptation is contained within this Bares Staff.\nIt can be developed by Refining a common Bares Staff.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Bares Staff of Temptation, Bares Staff</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10013</id>
			<name>Bares Longsword</name>
			<icon>00010013.png</icon>
			<desc>A longsword possessed with a hatred for all living things.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10039</id>
			<name>Ultimate Bares Longsword</name>
			<icon>00010013.png</icon>
			<desc>A Bares Longsword developed to its maximum potential.\nThere is a small chance this will be developed when Refining a common Bares Longsword.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Bares Longsword of Crimson Flame, Bares Longsword of Destruction, Bares Longsword of Temptation, Bares Longsword</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10038</id>
			<name>Bares Longsword of Temptation</name>
			<icon>00010013.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Temptation is contained within this Bares Longsword.\nIt can be developed by Refining a common Bares Longsword.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Bares Longsword of Temptation, Bares Longsword</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10037</id>
			<name>Bares Longsword of Destruction</name>
			<icon>00010013.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Destruction is contained within this Bares Longsword.\nIt can be developed by Refining a common Bares Longsword.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Bares Longsword of Destruction, Bares Longsword</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10036</id>
			<name>Bares Longsword of Crimson Flame</name>
			<icon>00010013.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Crimson Flame is contained within this Bares Longsword.\nIt can be developed by Refining a common Bares Longsword.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Bares Longsword of Crimson Flame, Bares Longsword</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10239</id>
			<name>Ultimate Bares Longbow</name>
			<icon>00010213.png</icon>
			<desc>A Bares Longbow developed to its maximum potential.\nThere is a small chance this will be developed when Refining a common Bares Longbow.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Bares Longbow of Crimson Flame, Bares Longbow of Destruction, Bares Longbow of Temptation, Bares Longbow</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10238</id>
			<name>Bares Longbow of Temptation</name>
			<icon>00010213.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Temptation is contained within this Bares Longbow.\nIt can be developed by Refining a common Bares Longbow.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Bares Longbow of Temptation, Bares Longbow</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10237</id>
			<name>Bares Longbow of Destruction</name>
			<icon>00010213.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Destruction is contained within this Bares Longbow.\nIt can be developed by Refining a common Bares Longbow.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Bares Longbow of Destruction, Bares Longbow</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10236</id>
			<name>Bares Longbow of Crimson Flame</name>
			<icon>00010213.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Crimson Flame is contained within this Bares Longbow.\nIt can be developed by Refining a common Bares Longbow.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Bares Longbow of Crimson Flame, Bares Longbow</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10213</id>
			<name>Bares Longbow</name>
			<icon>00010213.png</icon>
			<desc>A longbow possessed with a hatred for all living things.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10613</id>
			<name>Bares Axe</name>
			<icon>00010613.png</icon>
			<desc>An axe possessed with a hatred for all living things.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10638</id>
			<name>Bares Axe of Temptation</name>
			<icon>00010613.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Temptation is contained within this Bares Axe.\nIt can be developed by Refining a common Bares Axe.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Bares Axe of Temptation, Bares Axe</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10637</id>
			<name>Bares Axe of Destruction</name>
			<icon>00010613.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Destruction is contained within this Bares Axe.\nIt can be developed by Refining a common Bares Axe.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Bares Axe of Destruction, Bares Axe</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10636</id>
			<name>Bares Axe of Crimson Flame</name>
			<icon>00010613.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Crimson Flame is contained within this Bares Axe.\nIt can be developed by Refining a common Bares Axe.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Bares Axe of Crimson Flame, Bares Axe</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10639</id>
			<name>Ultimate Bares Axe</name>
			<icon>00010613.png</icon>
			<desc>A Bares Axe developed to its maximum potential.\nThere is a small chance this will be developed when Refining a common Bares Axe.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Bares Axe of Crimson Flame, Bares Axe of Destruction, Bares Axe of Temptation, Bares Axe</desc>
		</item>
	</makelist>
</itemInfo>

