<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<itemInfo>
	<itemKey>4802</itemKey>
	<itemName>Powder of Flame</itemName>
	<itemIcon>00004802.png</itemIcon>
	<itemDesc>A natural resource obtained through Gathering that can be employed to modify other materials using Alchemy.\n- How to Obtain: There’s a small chance of acquiring it from Rocks.</itemDesc>
	<collect>
		<character>
			<name>Copper</name>
		</character>
	</collect>
	<collect>
		<character>
			<name>Tin</name>
		</character>
	</collect>
	<node region="Imp Cave - Mining"/>
	<node region="Imp Cave - Mining"/>
	<node region="Coastal Cave - Mining"/>
	<node region="Forest of Seclusion - Mining"/>
	<node region="Northern Heidel Quarry - Mining"/>
	<node region="Mediah Shore - Mining"/>
	<makelist>
		<item>
			<id>10304</id>
			<name>Steel Dagger</name>
			<icon>00010304.png</icon>
			<desc>A sharp dagger made of steel.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10313</id>
			<name>Ultimate Steel Dagger</name>
			<icon>00010304.png</icon>
			<desc>A Steel Dagger developed to its maximum potential.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Steel Dagger of Crimson Flame, Steel Dagger of Destruction, Steel Dagger of Temptation, Steel Dagger</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10312</id>
			<name>Steel Dagger of Temptation</name>
			<icon>00010304.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Temptation is contained within this Steel Dagger.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Steel Dagger of Temptation, Steel Dagger</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10311</id>
			<name>Steel Dagger of Destruction</name>
			<icon>00010304.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Destruction is contained within this Steel Dagger.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Steel Dagger of Destruction, Steel Dagger</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10310</id>
			<name>Steel Dagger of Crimson Flame</name>
			<icon>00010304.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Crimson Flame is contained within this Steel Dagger.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Steel Dagger of Crimson Flame, Steel Dagger</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>13012</id>
			<name>Needle Trinket of Temptation</name>
			<icon>00013005.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Temptation is contained within this Needle Trinket.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Needle Trinket of Temptation, Needle Trinket</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>13011</id>
			<name>Needle Trinket of Destruction</name>
			<icon>00013005.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Destruction is contained within this Needle Trinket.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Needle Trinket of Destruction, Needle Trinket</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>13010</id>
			<name>Needle Trinket of Crimson Flame</name>
			<icon>00013005.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Crimson Flame is contained within this Needle Trinket.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Needle Trinket of Crimson Flame, Needle Trinket</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>14026</id>
			<name>Silver Embroidered Craftsman&apos;s Clothes</name>
			<icon>00014004.png</icon>
			<desc>A noble outfit made for Craftsmen.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>13013</id>
			<name>Ultimate Needle Trinket</name>
			<icon>00013005.png</icon>
			<desc>A Needle Trinket developed to its maximum potential.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Needle Trinket of Crimson Flame, Needle Trinket of Destruction, Needle Trinket of Temptation, Needle Trinket</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>13004</id>
			<name>Needle Trinket</name>
			<icon>00013005.png</icon>
			<desc>A trinket with a pouch full of needles.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10103</id>
			<name>Axion Shield</name>
			<icon>00010103.png</icon>
			<desc>A steel-plated shield used more for attacking than defending.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10111</id>
			<name>Axion Shield of Destruction</name>
			<icon>00010103.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Destruction is contained within this Axion Shield.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Axion Shield of Destruction, Axion Shield</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10110</id>
			<name>Axion Shield of Crimson Flame</name>
			<icon>00010103.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Crimson Flame is contained within this Axion Shield.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Axion Shield of Crimson Flame, Axion Shield</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10113</id>
			<name>Ultimate Axion Shield</name>
			<icon>00010103.png</icon>
			<desc>An Axion Shield developed to its maximum potential.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Axion Shield of Crimson Flame, Axion Shield of Destruction, Axion Shield of Temptation, Axion Shield</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10112</id>
			<name>Axion Shield of Temptation</name>
			<icon>00010103.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Temptation is contained within this Axion Shield.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Axion Shield of Temptation, Axion Shield</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10513</id>
			<name>Ultimate Jubre Talisman</name>
			<icon>00010504.png</icon>
			<desc>A Jubre Talisman developed to its maximum potential.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Jubre Talisman of Crimson Flame, Jubre Talisman of Destruction, Jubre Talisman of Temptation, Jubre Talisman</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10512</id>
			<name>Jubre Talisman of Temptation</name>
			<icon>00010504.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Temptation is contained within this Jubre Talisman.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Jubre Talisman of Temptation, Jubre Talisman</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10504</id>
			<name>Jubre Talisman</name>
			<icon>00010504.png</icon>
			<desc>An unknown ancient language is scribbled on this talisman.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10511</id>
			<name>Jubre Talisman of Destruction</name>
			<icon>00010504.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Destruction is contained within this Jubre Talisman.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Jubre Talisman of Destruction, Jubre Talisman</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10510</id>
			<name>Jubre Talisman of Crimson Flame</name>
			<icon>00010504.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Crimson Flame is contained within this Jubre Talisman.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Jubre Talisman of Crimson Flame, Jubre Talisman</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>24212</id>
			<name>Imperial Platinum Kettle</name>
			<icon>Pot_Base_47.png</icon>
			<desc>An imperial platinum kettle.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>24211</id>
			<name>Golden Hand Vase</name>
			<icon>Pot_Base_48.png</icon>
			<desc>A golden hand vase.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>24210</id>
			<name>Beautiful Opal Vase</name>
			<icon>Pot_Base_49.png</icon>
			<desc>A beautiful opal vase.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10704</id>
			<name>Oros Ornamental Knot</name>
			<icon>00010704.png</icon>
			<desc>A handmade ornamental knot for an axe lined with silver.</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10711</id>
			<name>Oros Ornamental Knot of Destruction</name>
			<icon>00010704.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Destruction is contained within this Oros Ornamental Knot.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Oros Ornamental Knot of Destruction, Oros Ornamental Knot</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10710</id>
			<name>Oros Ornamental Knot of Crimson Flame</name>
			<icon>00010704.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Crimson Flame is contained within this Oros Ornamental Knot.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Oros Ornamental Knot of Crimson Flame, Oros Ornamental Knot</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10713</id>
			<name>Ultimate Oros Ornamental Knot</name>
			<icon>00010704.png</icon>
			<desc>Oros Ornamental Knot developed to its maximum potential.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Oros Ornamental Knot of Crimson Flame, Oros Ornamental Knot of Destruction, Oros Ornamental Knot of Temptation, Oros Ornamental Knot</desc>
		</item>
		<item>
			<id>10712</id>
			<name>Oros Ornamental Knot of Temptation</name>
			<icon>00010704.png</icon>
			<desc>The energy of Temptation is contained within this Oros Ornamental Knot.\n\n- Repair to Max. Durability: Oros Ornamental Knot of Temptation, Oros Ornamental Knot</desc>
		</item>
	</makelist>
</itemInfo>

